

# Nishant Narayan

BRAND MANAGER

A progressively developed career spanned over 10 years ,Experienced Sales & Marketing Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Strong sales professional skilled in POS Material, Managing Accounts, BTL Activations, Point of Sale Advertising, and Business Relationship Management.

$\simeq$	nar.nishant@gmail.com	0585868997
Q	Al Nadha, Dubai, United Arab Emirates	08 March, 1985
in	linkedin.com/in/nishant-narayan-98b997a9	

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Brand Manager

CMS Retail Solutions

04/2019 – Present Dubai / UAE

Sales & Marketing

- Developing a lasting impression among clients. •
- Monitors market trends and oversees advertising and marketing activities.
- Researching & Developing impulsive marketing methods.
- Planning POSM displays execution in Market according to the standards of Modern trades.

#### MARKETING MANAGER

POP Creative FZE

05/2017 – 03/2019 Point Of Sales Advertisement Company

POSM Specialist

- Plan execute and close projects.
- Generating leads
- Meeting or exceeding sales goals
- Giving sales presentations to a range of prospective clients.
- Preparing weekly and monthly reports

#### COMMERCIAL MANAGER

## Brand People FZ

11/2012 - 05/2017

Sales and Logistics

2000,

Dubai / Media City / United Arab Emirates

- Targeting New Clients , Schedule meetings and Cold Calls
- Negotiate rates with local contractors and also international companies.
- Planning of procurement, production, inventory control, logistics and distribution to GCC countries Central Africa, Europe, North Africa, ACE and MENA regions.
- Having a passion for delivering excellent customer service in a cost-effective way.
- Preparing Import, Export, Free zone internal transfer documents based on the delivery schedule, using E-clearance facility of Dubai Customs.
- Coordinating with Operations for the timely delivery of the orders.
- Accuracy and on-time pickup and delivery.
- Determined the most cost-effective procedures and routes for shipments.
- Highly effective motivator with strong written and spoken communication skills.
- Proven ability to ensure that products are delivered in a good state and on time.

Sharjah / SAIF ZONE / UAE.

## **EDUCATION**

## Distance Education MBA [ Marketing] [Logistics]

Dubai

Courses

Marketing
Logistics

## **Bachelor Of Commerce**

India

Courses

Commerce

#### IELTS

DUBAI

#### HIGH SCHOOL

CBSE, INDIA

## PRIMARY SCHOOL

EMIRATES ENGLISH SPEAKING SCHOOL, DUBAI

## **SKILLS**



## LANGUAGES

ENGLISH Full Professional Proficiency HINDI Professional Working Proficiency MALAYALAM Full Professional Proficiency TAMIL Limited Working Proficiency